LEXI VESSELS

PROFILE

Enjoy's program development the most. Programming in JAVA and C for approximately 2 years. Has approximately one year of VDI experience. Worked with a team of students on multiple class projects. Current member of the Association for Computer Machinery.

EXPERIENCE

CASHIER, UNITED SUPERMARKET; ABILENE, TX- 2012-2014

Demonstrated ability to balance all transactions run through assigned register, including layaway payments, checks, register receipts, currency and credit card.

ATTENDANT, ANGELS OF CARE; ABILENE, TX - 2012-2014

Ensured that children were safe and had good behavior. Cared for children with mental and physical disabilities within the confines of their own home. Babysat children of all ages and genders and cared for them while their parents were away.

SACKER & CASHIER, MARKETSTREET; LUBBOCK, TX – 2010-2012 Highly proficient in the processes of exchanging and processing gift cards, travelers checks, food stamps, cash, checks, processing coupons and refunds.

EDUCATION

THE UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS AT SAN ANTONIO, SAN ANTONIO, TX – BACHELOR OF SCIENCE: COMPUTER SCIENCE, 2014-2018 GPA: 3.13 MAJOR GAP:3.63

SKILLS

Multiple years of experience in operating the cash register and maintaining a cash drawer. Well versed in performing monetary transactions such as giving and receiving change. Maintained a clean, net and correctly stocked check stand and safely secured work area. Proficient in Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Powerpoint, Microsoft Word, Java, C, Objective-C and Linux.